livenettv.to 2019-12-10

# Live NetTV [OFFICIAL Website] - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) describes how RaddixCore Solutions and its affiliates. (also referred to as “Raddixcore,” “Company,” “we,” “us,” or “our”), collects, stores, uses and protects your information when you use our website at <https://www.livenettv.sc/> (the “Site”), any mobile applications that hyperlink to this Policy and are available for download on this website or any other third party app store, or are pre-installed on third party devices (the “Apps”), or any other websites, pages, features, or content owned or operated by RaddixCore (collectively, including the Site and Apps, the “Services”).  
This Privacy Policy is part of, and is governed by, the terms and conditions set forth in our Terms of Service located at [TOS](https://www.livenettv.sc/tos.html). Please read the Terms of Service carefully before you use our Services.

* * *

### 1\. Acceptance of this Policy

By accessing, visiting or using our Services, you warrant and represent that you have read, understood and agreed to this Policy and our Terms of Service. If you disagree with anything in this Policy, you must not use or access the Services.

### 2\. Amendments to this Policy

We may periodically make changes to this Policy as we update or expand our Services. We will notify you of any material changes to this Privacy Policy by notifying you via the email we have on file for you, or by means of a notice on our Services in advance of the effective date of the changes. If you do not agree to the changes, you should discontinue your use of the Services prior to the time the modified Policy takes effect. If you continue using the Services after the modified Policy takes effect, you will be bound by the modified Policy.

Furthermore, we may provide you with “just-in-time” disclosures or additional information about the data collection, use and sharing practices of specific Services. These notices may provide more information about our privacy practices, or provide you with additional choices about how we process your personal information. 

### 3\. Information Collected through the Services

In this Policy, the term “personal information” includes any information that identifies or makes an individual identifiable. When you access or use our Services, we may generally collect the personal information described below.

A. Information Automatically Collected Through the Services  
We automatically collect information about you when you use the Services, such as:

Device Information: If you access the Services through a mobile device, we may be able to identify the general location using IP (not precise geolocation data), your mobile device’s brand, model, operating system, resolution, screen size, system version, Bluetooth settings, internet connection, random-access memory (“RAM”), the application you have installed, the applications you have running in the background, mobile device's advertising ID, other unique identifiers and other information related to device setting.

Cookies & Similar Tracking Information: We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to collect information about your interactions with our Services. The information we collect includes, but is not limited to, account activation time, content displayed to you and whether you clicked on it, advertisements displayed to you and whether you clicked on them, URLs you have visited, notifications that have appeared on your mobile device, your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, your mobile country code, and your user ID.

Content Sharing: When you choose to share content with us, we automatically collect information about your Wi-Fi connection.

### 4\. How We Use the Information We Collect

We use the personal information we gather through the Services for the purposes described below. If we use your personal information in any other ways, we will disclose this to you. You can choose not to share your information with third parties for marketing purposes, or from allowing us to use your personal information for any purpose that is incompatible with the purposes for which we originally collected it or subsequently obtained your consent. If you choose to limit the ways we can use your personal information, some or all of the Services may not be available to you.

To provide the Services to you. We require certain information from you in order to provide you with the Services you requested. Such information may include your contact and device information. We share this information with our service providers or partners to the extent necessary to continue to provide you with the Services. We cannot provide you with Services without such information.

To provide customer service. We process your personal information when you contact us to help you with any questions, concerns, disputes or issues, or to provide us with your feedback. Without your personal information, we cannot respond to you or ensure your continued use and enjoyment of the Services.

To enforce terms, agreements or policies. To ensure your safety and adherence to our terms, agreements or policies, we may process your personal information to: actively monitor, investigate, prevent and mitigate any alleged or actual prohibited, illicit or illegal activities on our Services; investigate, prevent, or mitigate violations of our terms and policies; enforce our agreements with third parties and partners; and, collect fees based on your use of our Services. We cannot perform our Services in accordance with our terms, agreements or policies without processing your personal information for such purposes.

To send you Service-related communications. We use your contact information to send you administrative or account-related information to you to keep you updated about our Services, inform you of relevant security issues or updates, or provide other transaction-related information to you. Service-related communications are not promotional in nature. You cannot unsubscribe from such communications because you could miss important developments relating to your account or the Services that may affect how you can use our Services.

For security purposes. We process your personal information to: improve and enforce our security measures; combat spam, malware, malicious activities or security risks; and to monitor and verify your identity so that unauthorized users do not access your account with us. We cannot ensure the security of our Services if we do not process your personal information for security purposes.

To maintain legal and regulatory compliance. We process your personal information to pay our taxes or fulfill our other business obligations, and/or to manage risk as required under applicable law. We cannot perform the Services in accordance with our legal and regulatory requirements without processing your personal information for such purposes.

To conduct research and development. We process information about the way you use and interact with our Services to: help us improve our Services; build new Services; and build customized features or Services. Such processing ensures your continued enjoyment of part or all of our Services.

To engage in marketing activities. We may process your contact information or information about your interactions on our Services to: send you marketing communications; deliver targeted marketing; inform you about events, webinars, or other materials, including those of our partners; and, keep you up-to-date with our relevant products and Services. Transactional communications about your account or our Services are not considered “marketing” communications. In addition, when you share your friends’ contact information with us, we may reach out to them to invite them to our Services and to continue receiving our communications. You can opt-out of our marketing activities at any time.

### 5\. How We Share Your Information with Third Parties

We may share your personal information with third parties in the following circumstances:

A. Employees, Third-Party Processors and Third-Party Service Providers

We disclose your personal information to our employees, contractors, affiliates, distributors, dealers, vendors and suppliers (“Service Providers”) who provide certain services to us or on our behalf, such as operating and supporting the Services, analyzing data, or performing marketing or consulting services. These Service Providers will only have access to the personal information needed to perform these limited functions on our behalf.

B. Third-Party Business Partners.

Base on you consent, we may work with and share some of your informaiton with our third-party advertising partners to provide you with advertisements or other tailored content. For more information about our own adversising practice and those of third-party partners. We may share information related to users of our service with affiliates or unaffiliated third parties on a de-identified, aggregate basis. While this informaiton will not identify you personally, in some instances these parties may be able to combile these aggregate ,de-identified informaiton with other data they have about you, or that they receive from other parties, in a manner that allows them to identify you personally. 

### 6\. Children

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 18 years old, unless permitted to do so by applicable law. Children are not permitted to use our Services unless they provide us with consent from their parent or guardian. If we become aware that we have unknowingly collected personal information from a child, we will make commercially reasonable efforts to delete such information in our database.

### 7\. Security

We are committed to ensuring the security of your personal information. We have physical, technical and administrative safeguards in place to protect the confidentiality of your personal information. In addition, we require that our service providers handling personal information also maintain appropriate physical, technical and administrative safeguards to protect the security and confidentiality of the personal information you provide to us.

However, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information or that loss, misuse, unauthorized acquisition, or alteration of your data will not occur. We also have no way of protecting any of your personal information that is not in our control, such as any information transmitted via email or wireless connections.

### 8\. How to Contact Us.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us: livenettv@tutamail.com.
